Two strangers fell in love. One knew it wasn't by chance.
Bounce is a drama, romance film directed by Don Roos.
Buddy Amaral, a successful and self-absorbed Los Angeles advertising executive, switches airline tickets with a stranger just
before boarding a long-delayed flight so that he might enjoy an overnight fling with a pretty Dallas businesswoman.
When the plane goes down, killing all aboard, Buddy's
guilt soon turns into an alcohol problem.
As part of his 12-step program, Buddy seeks atonement and decides
to seek out the woman he thinks he's left a widow.
Buddy Amaral, played by Ben Affleck.
Abby Janello, played by Gwyneth Paltrow.
Mimi Prager, played by Natasha Henstridge.
Greg Janello, played by Tony Goldwyn.
Seth, played by Johnny Galecki.
Jim Willer, played by Joe Morton.
Bounce is a 2000 American romantic drama film directed by Don
Roos, and starring Ben Affleck and Gwyneth Paltrow.
The film explores themes of stroke of fate, chance,
loss of loved one, widow, alcoholism.
The tone is emotional.